Preliminary Guide to the Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of Art archives department records, circa 1890-2007 COR0005.3.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Audiovisual and graphics records, circa 1869-2014; 1950-1984; Series 1; 24 Linear Feet
  - Audio and video tapes, 1965-1984; Series 1 Subseries 4
    - VHS: Fox 5 [unidentified], undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 59, Item 16)
    - VHS: Fox 5 Graphics Sei Hee Kim, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 59, Item 17)
    - Videocassette: ULAE Footage by John Lewis, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 59, Item 18)
    - Videocassette: AOL $30 million gift press preview master tape, 2000 February 5; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 59, Item 19)
    - Videocassette: MTV comes to the Corcoran for their Inaugural Party, 1997 January; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 59, Item 20)
    - Videocassette: Norman Rockwell- The Measure of the Man, 2000 September 14; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 59, Item 21)
    - Videocassette: Norman Rockwell- What Makes Him Good, 2000 September 14; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 59, Item 22)
    - Videocassette: Rockwell Painting Comes to Life, 2000 July 19; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 59, Item 23)
    - Videocassette: Ruby Bridges, 2000 August; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 59, Item 24)
    - Reel tape: Corcoran Gallery of Art Corcoran Tour, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 59, Item 25)
    - CD: Corcoran College of Art + Design, 2007-2008; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 59, Item 26)
    - CD: Corcoran College of Art + Design, 2007-2008; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 59, Item 27)
    - CD: Student Awards Ceremony, 2002; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 59, Item 28)
    - CD: Student Awards Certificate template, 2005-2006; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 59, Item 29)
    - CD: Student Ceremony, 2008; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 59, Item 30)
    - Where We Are: Photography Symposium transcriptions, 1978 February 25-26; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 59, Box 31)
    - VHS: Thomas Allen Harris: Heaven, Earth and Hell; Black Body; and Splash, 1991-1993; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 86, Item 1)
    - VHS: Unexpected Harmony Harriet Lesser's "Backstage Alaska" series, 1993; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 86, Item 2)
    - VHS: Lady Barton dialogue w/ 6 Writers Vietnam War Volunteers helping Vietmenese, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 86, Item 3)
    - VHS: For the Love of Paint Recent Works by Franklin White, 1993; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 86, Item 4)
    - VHS: Electronic Dialogue with Terrie Sultan on Contemporary Art, 1992; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 86, Item 5)
    - VHS: Women's Funk Art Making Party a Documentary, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 86, Item 6)
    - VHS: Lewis Desoto, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 86, Item 7)
    - VHS: Joysong Moskowitz: Time Language, Liquid Place and Beyond the Ring of Saturn, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 86, Item 8)
    - VHS: Douglas Kunin "Twist of Fate", undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 86, Item 9)
    - VHS: Susan Sterling: Ednia, Tzanko, Jesse, Mica, and Joe, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 86, Item 10)
    - VHS: Tom Nakashima "Screens and Other Works", 1995; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 86, Item 11)
    - VHS: Terrie Sultan's Gallery Talk on the 43rd Biennial of Contemporary Painting at the Corcoran Gallery of Art, 1993 October 30-1994 January 4; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 86, Item 12)
    - VHS: The Creative Moment: Artist at Work, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 86, Item 13)
    - VHS: Jiro Okura: Mountain Lake Workshop, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 86, Item 14)
    - VHS: Misson to Moscow, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 86, Item 15)
    - VHS: "Soundings" at the Corcoran Auditorium John Driscoll WPA New Music Series, 1988 Winter; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 86, Item 16)
    - VHS: Walt Disney Imagineering Herb Ryman Interview: 60 Minutes Show Looop, 1992; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 86, Item 17)
    - VHS: Henrietta Mantoot, 1994 April 18; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 86, Item 18)
    - VHS: Performance Art and Video Workshop, 1988; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 86, Item 19)
    - VHS: Significant Losses AIDS Quilt, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 86, Item 20)
    - VHS: Albert Paley: Man of Steel, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 86, Item 21)
    - VHS: Ken Aptekar Four Questions, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 86, Item 22)
    - VHS: Phillip Mallory Jones: Soldiers of a Recent and Forgotten War, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 86, Item 23)
    - VHS: Eyvind Earle "Seventy-five Years", undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 86, Item 24)
    - VHS: Wiley's Tower, 1991 May 31; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 86, Item 25)
    - VHS: Pscal: Reflections in Glass Women Artist Carving Glass Sculpture, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 86, Item 26)
    - VHS: "Soundings" Mark Vargas WPA New Music Series, 1988 Winter; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 86, Item 27)
    - VHS: Margot Kernan Watching, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 86, Item 28)
    - VHS: 60 Minutes: Tin Man, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 86, Item 29)
    - VHS: Art Stokes Program #24, 1991 October 5; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 86, Item 30)
    - VHS: Helene Aylon A Proposal for: Current: two sacs en route, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 86, Item 31)
    - VHS: Hunger: Performance Video, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 86, Item 32)
    - VHS: America's Defense Monitor: War Through the Eyes of the Artists, 1991; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 86, Item 33)
    - VHS: Tracy, Stephanie, Jason and Amy, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 86, Item 34)
    - VHS: Timeless Treasures: Miniature Art, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 86, Item 35)
    - VHS: Renee Butler Reflection Space, 1997; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 86, Item 36)
    - VHS: The Tower of the Potomac Volume 1: Orientation, 1994 October 4; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 86, Item 37)
    - VHS: The Tower of the Potomac Volume 2: An Electronic Unveiling, 1994 October 6; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 86, Item 38)
    - VHS: The Tower of the Potomac Program 3: Mo Edoga: A Non-Euclidean Dialogue, 1994 October 6; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 86, Item 39)
    - U-Matic: Philip Morris incorporated PSA/Corcoran Gallery music Terry Allen, Green Shoes Publishing Second Western States 38th Corocran Biennial, 1983 January 10; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 87, Item 1)
    - Reel: Black Folk Art in America: 1930-1980 The Corcoran Gallery of Art 1" Master, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 87, Item 2)
    - U-Matic: Pennsylvania Academy of the Fine Arts Arthur B. Carles: Painting with Color, 1983 September 23-November 27; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 87, Item 3)
    - Reel: Voices of America Wendy Ross interview with film director Dennis Hopper, 1971 July 9; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 87, Item 4)
    - Reel: Voices of America Wendy Ross interviews Dennis Hopper about exhibit at Corcoran, 1971 July 9; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 87, Item 5)
    - Reel: Tape #1, 1978 February 26; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 87, Item 6)
    - Reel: Tape #2, 1978 February 26; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 87, Item 7)
    - Reel: Tape #3, 1978 February 26; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 87, Item 8)
    - Reel: Tape #4, 1978 February 26; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 87, Item 9)
    - Reel: Tape #5, 1978 February 26; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 87, Item 10)
    - Reel: Tape #6, 1978 February 26; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 87, Item 11)
    - Reel: Corcoran photography symposium, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 87, Item 12-19)
    - Cassette: Washington's Fine Arts Stations Mrs. Take Tabor, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 87, Item 20)
    - DVD: Lane Twitchell Corcoran, 2004 March 22; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 87, Item 21)
    - DVD: The Corcoran Gallery of Art [Permanent collection] TIFF Disc 01, 2006; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 1)
    - DVD: The Corcoran Gallery of Art [Permanent collection] TIFF Disc 02, 2006; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 2)
    - DVD: The Corcoran Gallery of Art [Permanent collection] TIFF Disc 03, 2006; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 3)
    - DVD: The Corcoran Gallery of Art [Permanent collection] TIFF Disc 04, 2006; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 4)
    - DVD: The Corcoran Gallery of Art [Permanent collection] TIFF Disc 05, 2006; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 5)
    - DVD: The Corcoran Gallery of Art [Permanent collection] TIFF Disc 06, 2006; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 6)
    - DVD: The Corcoran Gallery of Art [Permanent collection] TIFF Disc 07, 2006; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 7)
    - DVD: The Corcoran Gallery of Art [Permanent collection] TIFF Disc 08, 2006; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 8)
    - DVD: The Corcoran Gallery of Art [Permanent collection] TIFF Disc 09, 2006; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 9)
    - DVD: The Corcoran Gallery of Art [Permanent collection] TIFF Disc 10, 2006; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 10)
    - DVD: The Corcoran Gallery of Art [Permanent collection] TIFF Disc 11, 2006; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 11)
    - DVD: The Corcoran Gallery of Art [Permanent collection] TIFF Disc 12, 2006; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 12)
    - DVD: The Corcoran Gallery of Art [Permanent collection] TIFF Disc 13, 2006; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 13)
    - DVD: The Corcoran Gallery of Art [Permanent collection] TIFF Disc 14, 2006; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 14)
    - DVD: The Corcoran Gallery of Art [Permanent collection] TIFF Disc 15, 2006; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 15)
    - DVD: The Corcoran Gallery of Art [Permanent collection] TIFF Disc 16, 2006; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 16)
    - DVD: The Corcoran Gallery of Art [Permanent collection] TIFF Disc 17, 2006; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 17)
    - DVD: The Corcoran Gallery of Art [Permanent collection] TIFF Disc 18, 2006; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 18)
    - DVD: The Corcoran Gallery of Art [Permanent collection] TIFF Disc 19, 2006; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 19)
    - DVD: The Corcoran Gallery of Art [Permanent collection] TIFF Disc 21, 2006; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 20)
    - DVD: The Corcoran Gallery of Art [Permanent collection] TIFF Disc 22, 2006; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 21)
    - DVD: The Corcoran Gallery of Art [Permanent collection] TIFF Disc 23, 2006; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 22)
    - DVD: The Corcoran Gallery of Art [Permanent collection] TIFF Disc 24, 2006; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 23)
    - DVD: The Corcoran Gallery of Art [Permanent collection] TIFF Disc 25, 2006; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 24)
    - DVD: The Corcoran Gallery of Art [Permanent collection] TIFF Disc 26, 2006; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 25)
    - DVD: The Corcoran Gallery of Art [Permanent collection] TIFF Disc 27, 2006; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 26)
    - DVD: The Corcoran Gallery of Art [Permanent collection] JPEGs Discs 01 and 02, 2006 April; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 27)
    - DVD: The Corcoran Gallery of Art [Permanent collection] JPEGs Discs 03 and 04, 2006 April; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 28)
    - DVD: The Corcoran Gallery of Art [Permanent collection] JPEGs Discs 05 and 06, 2006 April; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 29)
    - DVD: The Corcoran Gallery of Art [Permanent collection] JPEGs Discs 07 thru 10, 2006 April; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 30)
    - DVD: The Corcoran Gallery of Art [Permanent collection] JPEGs Discs 11 and 12, 2006 May; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 31)
    - DVD: The Corcoran Gallery of Art [Permanent collection] JPEGS Discs 013 thru 018, 2006 May; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 32)
    - DVD: The Corcoran Gallery of Art [Permanent collection] JPEGS Discs 019 and 020, 2006 June; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 33)
    - DVD: The Corcoran Gallery of Art [Permanent collection] JPEGS Discs 021 thru 024, 2006 June; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 34)
    - DVD: The Corcoran Gallery of Art [Permanent collection] JPEGS Discs 025 thru 027, 2006 June; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 35)
    - DVD: The Corcoran Gallery of Art [Permanent collection] Disc 01, 2004; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 36-39)
    - DVD: The Corcoran Gallery of Art [Permanent collection] Disc 01 Printer files, 2004; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 40)
    - DVD: The Corcoran Gallery of Art [Permanent collection] Disc 01 Review/thumbnail/database files, 2004; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 41)
    - DVD: The Corcoran Gallery of Art [Permanent collection] Disc 11a, 2003; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 42)
    - DVD: The Corcoran Gallery of Art [Permanent collection] Disc 11b, 2003; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 43)
    - DVD: The Corcoran Gallery of Art [Permanent collection] Disc 10a, 2002; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 44-45)
    - DVD: The Corcoran Gallery of Art [Permanent collection] Disc 10b, 2002; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 46-48)
    - DVD: The Corcoran Gallery of Art [Permanent collection] Disc 01 Tiffs (New Series), undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 50-52)
    - DVD: The Corcoran Gallery of Art [Permanent collection] Tiffs Disc 1, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 53)
    - DVD: The Corcoran Gallery of Art [Permanent collection] Tiffs Disc 2, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 54)
    - DVD: The Corcoran Gallery of Art [Permanent collection] Tiffs Disc 3, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 55)
    - DVD: The Corcoran Gallery of Art [Permanent collection] Tiffs Disc 4, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 56)
    - DVD: The Corcoran Gallery of Art [Permanent collection] Tiffs Disc 5, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 57)
    - DVD: The Corcoran Gallery of Art [Permanent collection] Tiffs Disc 6, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 58)
    - DVD: The Corcoran Gallery of Art [Permanent collection] Tiffs Disc 7, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 59)
    - DVD: Christopher Pearse Cranch-Castle Gandolfo, Lake Albano, Italy 1852, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 60)
    - DVD: Frank Blackwell Mayer-Leisure and Labor 1858, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 61)
    - DVD: Hiram Powers-The Greek Slave modeled 1841-1843, carved 1846, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 62)
    - DVD: Escobar Marisol-The Large Family Group 1957, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 63)
    - DVD: Marisol Escobar-The Large Family Group 1957, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 64)
    - DVD: Charles Demuth-Rooftops and Trees 1918, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 65)
    - DVD: Everett Shinn-Cross Streets of New York 1899, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 66)
    - DVD: Grace Hartigan-Summer Street 1956, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 67)
    - DVD: De Witt Clinton Boutelle-Trenton Falls Near Utica, New York 1876, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 68)
    - DVD: Garry Winogrand-Albuquerque, New Mexico 1958, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 69)
    - DVD: Yevgeny Khaldei-Victory Flag over Reichstag, Berlin, 1945, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 70)
    - DVD: Noah Purifoy-Untitled (Assemblage) 1967, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 71)
    - DVD: Kerry James Marshall, Voyager, 1992, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 72)
    - DVD: Daniel Garber-Ellicott City, Afternoon 1940, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 73)
    - DVD: Aaron Douglas-Into Bondage 1936, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 74)
    - DVD: Cecelia Beaux-Portrait of Julia Kahle 1925-1926, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 75)
    - DVD: Gordon Parks-Department Store, Birmingham, Alabama 1956, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 76)
    - DVD: Larry Rivers-Packing the Dutch Masters, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 77)
    - DVD: James Amos Porter-Ticket-Taker at Griffith Stadium c. 1944, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 78)
    - DVD: Carleton E. Watkins-River View of Royal Arches, Yosemite 1861, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 79)
    - DVD: Rob Fischer-They Shoot Horses, Don't They? 2008, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 80)
    - DVD: Old Corcoran (Renwick) building facade CGA Archives, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 81)
    - DVD: Ornamental metalwork Corcoran Gallery of Art Roof conservation documentation Disc 1 of 2, 2010 May 8; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 82)
    - DVD: Ornamental metalwork Corcoran Gallery of Art Roof conservation documentation Disc 2 of 2, 2010 May 8; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 83)
    - DVD: Rotunda Chan Chao, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 84)
    - DVD: Corcoran Gallery eps files, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 88, Item 85)
    - DVD: John Singer Sargent-Bedouin Women 1890-1891, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 89, Item 1)
    - DVD: George Wesley Bellows-Forty-two Kids, 1907, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 89, Item 2)
    - DVD: Childe Hassam-Mt. Hood (Oregon) 1904, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 89, Item 3)
    - DVD: Anne Truitt-Insurrection 1962 (2 copies), undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 89, Item 4)
    - DVD: John La Farge-Flowers on a Window Ledge 1861, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 89, Item 5)
    - DVD: Thomas Gainsborough-Francis Basset, Lord de Dunstanville 1786, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 89, Item 6)
    - DVD: Arthur Bowen Davies-The Great Mother 1914, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 89, Item 8)
    - DVD: Ronald Bladen-The X 1967, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 89, Item 9)
    - DVD: John Storrs-Le Sergent de Ville-Modeled by 1919, cast c. 1923, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 89, Item 10)
    - DVD: Frederic Edwin Church-Niagara 1857 (2 copies), undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 89, Item 11)
    - DVD: George Peter Alexander Healy-James K. Polk 1846, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 89, Item 12)
    - DVD: Eliphalet Frazer Andrews-Rutherford Birchard Hayes 1881, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 89, Item 13)
    - DVD: Horace Bonham-Nearing the Issue at the Cockpit 1870, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 89, Item 14)
    - DVD: Mary Cassatt-Young Girl at a Window c. 1883-1885, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 89, Item 15)
    - DVD: Gari Melchers-Penelope 1910, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 89, Item 16)
    - DVD: Samuel Finley Breese Morse-The House of Representatives completed 1822, probably reworked 1823, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 89, Item 17)
    - DVD: Posters, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 89, Item 18)
    - DVD: Salon Dore, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 89, Item 19)
    - DVD: Salon Dore digital images, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 89, Item 20)
    - DVD: Mantle Room, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 89, Item 21)
    - DVD: Color & Light as Object Photos discs 1-3, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 89, Item 22)
    - DVD: Installation Shoots of exhibition titled "Now", "Renunciation", and "Rage, Love, Hope & Desire", undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 89, Item 23)
    - DVD: Spencer Finch-My Business With the Cloud, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 89, Item 24)
    - DVD: Installation Shoots of exhibition titled "STRANGE FRUIT" by Hank Willis and A Drawing from the Collection, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 89, Item 25)
    - DVD: Claire Healy and Sean Cordeiro-Are We There Yet?, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 89, Item 26)
    - DVD: 30 Americans discs 1-3, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 89, Item 27)
    - DVD: Shadow of History & Sleeping Soldiers, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 89, Item 28)
    - DVD: Object & Exhibition Photography discs 1-2, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 89, Item 29)
    - DVD: Object Photography, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 89, Item 30)
    - DVD: Object Photography, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 89, Item 31)
    - DVD: Object Photography, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 89, Item 32)
    - DVD: Object Photography, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 89, Item 33)
    - DVD: Object Photography/Painting, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 89, Item 34)
    - DVD: Object Photography, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 89, Item 35)
    - DVD: 2-D and 3-D objects, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 89, Item 36)
    - DVD: 2-D and 3-D objects, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 89, Item 37)
    - DVD: Object Photography, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 89, Item 38)
    - DVD: Object Photography, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 89, Item 39)
    - DVD: Object Photography, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 89, Item 40)
    - DVD: Recent Acquisitions, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 89, Item 41)
    - DVD: Chan Chao-New Object Photography, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 89, Item 42)
    - DVD: Peale in France, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 89, Item 43)
    - DVD: Corbis 128 image files, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 89, Item 44)
    - DVD: Corbis 128 image files, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 89, Item 45)
    - DVD: Carpets-Photos by Sotheby's, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 89, Item 46)
    - DVD: Images discs 11-15, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 89, Item 47)
    - DVD: Women's Committee Acquisitions discs 1-2, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 89, Item 48)
    - DVD: Corcoran-Chim (David Seymour), undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 89, Item 49)
    - DVD: Not Accessible?, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 89, Item 50)
    - DVD: Corcoran Paintings Hi-Res Scans discs 1-2, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 89, Item 51)
    - DVD: DeKooning, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 89, Item 52)
    - DVD: William Picknell-The Road to Concarneau, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 89, Item 53)
    - DVD: Frederick Childe Hassam-The New York Window 1912, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 89, Item 54)
    - DVD: William McGregor Paxton-The Hose Maid 1910, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 89, Item 55)
    - DVD: Theodore Robinson-The Layette 1892, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 89, Item 56)
    - DVD: Thomas Easkins-Singing a Pathetic Song 1881, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 89, Item 57)
    - DVD: Abbott Handerson Thayer-Self-portrait 1919, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 89, Item 58)
    - DVD: Albert Besnard-Portrait of Senator Clark 1899, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 89, Item 59)
    - DVD: Circle of Rembrandt van Rijn-Man with Sheet of Music 17th century, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 89, Item 60)
    - DVD: Dish with Allegorical Scene c. 1520-1525, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 89, Item 61)
    - DVD: Dish with an Allegorical Subject, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 89, Item 62)
    - DVD: Small Ispahan Rug, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 89, Item 63)
    - DVD: Large Esfahan Herat Rug early 17th century, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 89, Item 64)
    - DVD: Plate with a Portrait of a Woman (Camilla) 1541, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 89, Item 65)
    - DVD: Francesco Xanto Avelli-Plate with the Massacre of the Innocents c.1527-1530, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 89, Item 66)
    - DVD: Giovanni Boldini-After the Bath after 1889, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 89, Item 67)
    - DVD: Jean Baptiste Henri Deshays-Personification of Music 18th century, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 89, Item 68)
    - DVD: Hillaire-Germain-Edgar Degas-Ecole de danse c. 1873, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 89, Item 69)
    - DVD: Johan Barthold Jongkind-Zoutveau Polder near Delft 1890, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 89, Item 70)
    - DVD: Charles Bird King-Poor Artist's Cupboard c. 1815, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 89, Item 71)
    - DVD: John Marin-Flint Isle, Maine-No. 1 1947, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 89, Item 72)
    - DVD: John Wesley Jarvis-General Jacob Jennings Brown c. 1815, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 89, Item 73)
    - DVD: Albert Bierstadt-Buffalo Trail: The Impending Storm 1869, undated; Series 1 subseries 4 (Box 89, Item 74)